Guide to the NURTUREart records CBHM.0025
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 1: Artists' Registry
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z Files
    - Mazza, Jennifer, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - McCabe, Richard B., circa 2005 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - McCaig, Melissa, circa 2000 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - McCallen, Susan, circa 2004 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - McCarron, Maureen, circa 2003 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - McCluskey, Corrie, circa 2001 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - McConnell, Julie, circa 2005 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - McDonald, Anne, circa 2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - McEwin, Florence, circa 2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - McGarry, Patrick, circa 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - McGee, Nancy, circa 2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - McHarry, Colette M., circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - McGrath, Jim, circa 2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - McMinn, Kylie, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - McMunn-Coffran, Cameron, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Meacham, Ray, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Meagher, Patrick, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Medina, Ada, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Mehling, Robert, circa 2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Mein, Jessica, circa 2007 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Melas, Eva, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Melin, Kristin Ann, circa 2003 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Mellon, Joan, circa 2007 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Mendez De Hoyos, Enrique, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Menocal, Ramon, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Merisier, Emmanuel, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Merrell, James, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Mertes-Frady, Gudrun, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Messiah, Norman, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Meule, Loura Van Der, circa 2007 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Meyer, David, circa 2005 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Mikhailov, Anatole, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Milionis, Cynthia, circa 2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Millar, Steven, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Amy, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Mills, PJ, circa 2008 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Milo, Sabrina, circa 2000 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Milroy, Mark, circa 2004 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Milu, J., circa 2003 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Minchillo, Desi, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Minervini, Lucia, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bernhard Minoggio, Uli, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Mitchelle, Brandon C., 2008 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Mitchelle, Gail Robin, circa 2005 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Mitcham, Jason, circa 2010 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Miyamori, Keiko, circa 2001 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Miyazi, Hiroshi, circa 2005 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Mizrachi, Alice, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Moise, Mirelle, circa 2000 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Mola, Kelly, circa 2005 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Molloy, Traci J., circa 2007 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Molly, MIchael, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Monnier, Annette, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Moore, Cindy Stockton, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Moore, Tom, circa 2000 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Morale', D.C., 2008 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Morganstern, Andrea, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Moreau, Andrea, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Moretti, Manola, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Morgan, Heather, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Morgan, Janet, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Morgan, Michael, circa 2001 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Moriarty, Laura, circa 2006 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Morillas, Mauricio, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Morioka, Juri, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Moriya, Koji, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Moroney, Kathleen, circa 2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Moriyama, Tadashi, circa 2007 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Morris, Dean, circa 2003 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Morrison, Joel, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Morrison, John, circa 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Morton, Ella, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Morton, Joshua L., circa 2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Moses, Micah, circa 2003 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Mosley, Walter, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Motta, Carlos, circa 2006 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Moulton, Shana, circa 2006 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Movius, John, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Mudge, Kelly, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Mukhtar, Helene, circa 2007 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Mullen, Michael, circa 2001 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Munich, Becky, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Munoz, Susan, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Murphy, Margaret, circa 2003 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Murphy, Mary Catania, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Murphy, Ryan Sarah, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Mustric, Stephanie, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Myrie, Eliza, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Nadzieia, Elisa, circa 2000 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Nagy, Jenene, circa 2006 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Nakamura, Hiroyuki, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Najarian, Arpie Gennetian, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Nam, Hyo-Jeong, circa 2007 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Namba, Naomi, circa 2006 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Naughton, John Patrick, circa 2005 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Nazzoli, Maria, circa 2005 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Neal, Jon, circa 2002 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Neblett, Marcia, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Neilson, Heidi, circa 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Neff, Heidi, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Nelson, Guy Arthur, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Nevelson, Maria, circa 2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Newman, Mari Mae, circa 2001 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Newmark, Alexandra, circa 2004 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Newson, Becky, circa 2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Huong, Ngo, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Nguyen, Stephen, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Nicholls, Sarah, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Nirenberg, Michael, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Norkin, Michael, circa 2003 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Norman, Elaine, circa 2004 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Norman Spencer, Lucy, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Nurkse, Lucille, circa 2003 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Nussear, Caleb, circa 2009 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Nusser, Erika, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Oakes, Julie, circa 2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Oates, Leah, circa 2006 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Occhiogrosso, Gina, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Oda, Yuko, circa 2007 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Ogier-Bloomer, Anna, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Ohashi, Atsushi, circa 2005 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Oka, Seiko, circa 2006 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Olah, Janell, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Oldenburg, Aaron, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Olenick, Iviva, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Olin, Mike, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Olivier, Nancy, circa 2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Olsen, Damien, circa 2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - O'Neil, Rob, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - O'Rourke, Janell, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Orling, Emily, circa 2001 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - O'Rourke, Patricia, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Osman, Laimah, circa 2002 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Overbay, Paula, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Overbeay, Donald, circa 2002 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Overton, Allison, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Owenns, Jimmy, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Ozmenoglu, Ardan, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Pacheco, Gabriel Rueda, circa 2007 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Paik, Younhee, circa 2006 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Pak, Jinnine, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Palileo, Maia, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Palmer, Marcy, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Palmerton, Elwyn, circa 2004 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Pappa, Kenneth, circa 2000 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Park, Aegi Changsuk, circa 2006 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Park, Cheo-Reom, circa 2004 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Park, Jihyun, circa 2003 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Park, Jung Eun, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Parris, Bridget, circa 2008 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Parsons, Tara, circa 2006 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Pasila, Joanne, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Pattara, Subhorn, circa 2008 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Patterson, Helen, circa 2006 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Patterson, Katherine McDowell, circa 2007 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Paulsen, James I., 2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Paulson, Sarah H., circa 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Pedlow, Sara, circa 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Pelaez-Dorian, Linda, circa 2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Pelli, Leemour, circa 2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Peng, Qi, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Penn, Gelah, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Peppito, Julie, circa 2004 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Perici, Gabriele, circa 2004 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Perpinal, Dalit Gurevich, circa 2002 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Perrine, Doreen, circa 2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Perry, Vicky, circa 2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Perschke, Kurt, circa 2006 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Pervin, Gilda, circa 2004 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Peters, Josh, circa 2005 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Petino, Carol, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Petrov, Daniel, circa 2006 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Phillips, Rachel, circa 2009 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, Tracy, circa 2005 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Philp, Lawrence, circa 2000 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Pingree, Meridith, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Pinna, Alex, circa 2001 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Pinto, Mary, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Piscioneri, Kathleen, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Pizzani, Lucia, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Planisek, Mark, circa 2005 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Plate, Catya, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Plecs, Chris, circa 2008 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Pober Rittenberg, Ellen, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pocklington, Jamie, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Pohle, Mirko, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Polashenski, Anne, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Pollman, Justin, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Polumbo, Randy, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Posch, Josefina, circa 2006 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Power, Mark, circa 2005 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Prest, Mel, circa 2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Pratt, Sandra, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Preston, Maggie, circa 2008 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Prine, Shane, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Provenzano, Michelle, circa 2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Prunty, Jason, circa 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Purcigliotti, Andrea, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Puller, Gunter, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Purdy, Dianne, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Puri, Antonio Alexander, circa 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Püttgen, Julie, circa 2007 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Quisgard, Liz Whitney, circa 2005 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Quirk, Christopher, circa 2005 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Rabbia, Luisa, circa 2001 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Rabinovich, Raquel, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Rachko, Barbara, circa 2001 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Racine, Ross, circa 2007 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Radinovsky, Dean, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Radsprecher, Carol, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Rahmani, Aviva, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Ramey, Catherine, circa 2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ramirex, Javier, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ramsay, Debra, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Ramsay, Lisa, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Rasch, circa 2007 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Ray, Lynda, circa 2009 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Razin, Aleksandr, circa 2007 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Ream, Annelise, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Reeder, James, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Rehm, Cindy, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Rehm, Kyle, circa 2003 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Reid, Leah, circa 2007 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Reiger, Christopher, circa 2006 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Reiger, Christopher, circa 2008 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Reiman, James, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Reinemann, Eric, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Reinhardt, Kimberly, circa 2004 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Rene, Simone, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Reneke, Margaret, circa 2001 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Reynolds, Andrienne, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Richardson, Lynn, circa 2008 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Riley, Elizabeth, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Rinklin, Cristi, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Ritz, Lorna, circa 2003 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Rivera Toro, Quintin, circa 2003 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Robbiani, Daniele, circa 2004 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Roberts, Laura, circa 2002 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Robinson, Amie, circa 2005 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Dorothy, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Rockwell, Roxene, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Rodrigues, Christopher, circa 2006 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Rodriguez, Jorge-Luis, circa 2003 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Rodriguez, Mark, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Rodriguez, Riche, circa 1998 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rodriguez, Ritchard, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Roedenbeck, Elise, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rogers, Brooke, circa 2007 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Roleke, Margaret, circa 2006 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Rolfe, Wendy, circa 2005 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Romer, Bryony, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Rooney, Autumn, circa 2004 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Roselli, Grace, circa 2006 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Rosen, Ann, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Rosenberg, Maddy, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Rosenthal, Charles J., circa 2006 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Rosner, Alan, circa 1998 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Ross, Jennifer, circa 2001 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Ross, Robin, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Susan, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Roth, Martin, circa 2003 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Rowland, Jake, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Rudd, Timothy, circa 2003 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Russell, Audrey Hasen, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Ruff, Regina, circa 2008 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Ruff, Michael, circa 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Russell, Audrey Hasen, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ryan, Jennifer, circa 2004 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Ryan, Michael, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Ryer, Evan Reehl, circa 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Safren, Cheryl, circa 2003 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Saito, Kiyomitsu, circa 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Saito, Yoshiyuki, circa 2001 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Salamandra, Linda, circa 2007 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Salerno, Kim, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Salmanson, Carol, circa 2007 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Salmon, Jennifer C., 2008 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Saltarelli, Valerio, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Samitz, Debra, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Samson, Gina, circa 2006 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Samuels, Janie, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Sanchez, Jennifer, circa 2006 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Santaniello, Carmine, circa 2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Sarteschi, Jamison, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Sass, Julie, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Sato, Hidemi, circa 2004 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Sauer, Dick, circa 2000 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Savannah, Gae, circa 2003 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Saville, Lynn, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Sawtell, Scott, circa 2006 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Scarlett, Sunny, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Schaefer, Barbara, circa 2001 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Schaer, Miriam, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Scharbach, Jake, circa 2008 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Schenker, Irys, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Scherrer, Melissa, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Schiele, Kristen, circa 2007 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Schille, Carol, circa 2000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Schloss, Sima, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Schenker, Irvs, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Schmertz, Diana, circa 2007 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Schmidt, Mark, circa 2003 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Schmidt, Patrick, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Schneider, Jeff, circa 2003 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Schneider, Tina, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Schooley, Cynthia, circa 2003 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Schroth, Peter, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Schulz, David, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Schurr, Thomas, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Schwadron, Julia, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Schwartz, Molly, circa 2008 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Schwartz, Sylvia, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Schwadron, Julia, circa 2008 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Schweiger, Rebecca, circa 2007 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Schweitzer, Jeffery R., circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Scott, Darcy, circa 2001 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Scott, Lauren, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Scrapworm, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Scullion, Gil, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Seaberg, Libby, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Secka, Steven, circa 2007 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Seeger, Zach, circa 2005 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Sehr, Katie, circa 2006 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Seldom, Harry, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Sergent, Jean-Pierre, circa 2002 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Serino, Jamie, circa 2000 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Serra-Jovenich, Marta Luz, circa 2001 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Shachnow, Audrey, circa 2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Shandler, Manju, circa 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Shanker, Marc, circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Shannon, Cate, circa 2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Sharp, Keith, circa 2001 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Shaver, Sharon, circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Shea, Dana, circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Sheehan, Ross I., circa 2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Sher, Vicki, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Sherman, Mary, circa 2005 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Shield, Sonja, circa 2005 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Shim, Jeong Eun, circa 2004 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Shin, Hyungsub, circa 2003 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Shin, Sang-Ho, circa 2005 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Shirobayashi, Kiriko, circa 2006 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Shpungen, Diana and Engelmann, Nicole, circa 2003 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Shuster, Wendy, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Sibbers-Tuthill, Alison, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Siber, Matt, circa 2005 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Silber-Delerive, Toni, circa 2006 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Sillen-Gledhill, Kim, circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Silva, Mario, circa 2005 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Silverman, Robert, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Silvers, Regina, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Simon, Deborah, circa 2006 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Simmons, Philip, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Simonian, Judith, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Simpson, Kimberly, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Sissman, Liron, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Skrzynski, Jackie, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Slein, Alison, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Sleurs, Jason, circa 2006 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Slitkin, Barbara Ann, circa 2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Small, Andrew, circa 2008 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Smiedt, Stephanie, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Smith, Adam Parker, circa 2006 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Jennifer, circa 2007 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Smith Jr., Anthony, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Rene, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Shinique, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Winslow, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Smolarz, Elizabeth, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Smothers, Mel, circa 2007 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Sobel, Sheila, circa 2001 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Smudge Studio, circa 2006 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Soligno, Matilde, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Soller, Helaine, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Solmi, Federico, circa 2004 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Somogyi, Ted, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Soreff, Stephen, circa 2005 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Sotelo, Mano, circa 2007 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Sourget, Amelie, circa 2004 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Southworth, Travis LeRoy, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Spear, Duston, circa 2006 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Spector, Maria, circa 2006 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Spies, Anne-Katrin, circa 2008 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Sprecher, Jered, circa 2004 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Springer, Dan, circa 1998 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Springfield, Molly, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - St. Germain, Michael, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - St-Jacques, Pierre, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Staelin, Kay, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Staiger, Alexandra, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Staiger, Melissa, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Stanislav, Andrea, circa 2004 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Stayrook, Chad, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Steckbauer, Melissa, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Stecko, Kathy, circa 2007 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Stefanni, Norma, circa 1999 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Steffy, Melinda, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Stein, Anna, circa 2009 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Steinhauer, Eddie, circa 2001 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Steinke, Krista Leigh, circa 2008 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Steinsnyder, Bonnie, circa 2002 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Stenger, Jeremy, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Stephanie, Colleen McCubbin, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Stephan, Maureen, circa 2003 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Stewart, Betsy, circa 2001 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Still, Sam, circa 2001 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Stockton, Mark, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Stoller, Jessica M., circa 2006 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Stolz-Robert, Catherine, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Stoltzfus, Randall, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Strackbein / Tisa, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Stricke, Mindy, circa 2005 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Stuelke, Satre, circa 2002 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Stuttman, Paula, circa 2006 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Sullivan, Grace, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Sullivan, Jennifer, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Sumichrast, Jozef, 2005 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Summanen, Grace, circa 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Sunshine, Ilene, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Surbone, Giustina, circa 2005 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Susman, Dru, circa 2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sussman, Rachel, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Suzuki, Futaba, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Suzuki, Naoe, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Swack, Debra, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Swan, Philip G., circa 2007 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Szczesny, Radek, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Taber, Mark G., 2007 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Tadei, Marialuisa, circa 2004 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Talbot, Nina, circa 2005 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Taliano, Lisa, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Talluto, Amy, circa 2005 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Tam, Karen, circa 2007 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Tamayo, Amy, circa 2000 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Tameda, Atsushi, circa 2004 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Tanaka, Kikuko, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Tarantino, Ann, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Tarbi, Michael, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Tark, Soon-Ae, circa 2007 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Taruishi, Naho, 2009 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Tan, Tattfoo, circa 2006 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Tassin, Denise, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Tataro, Vera, circa 2007 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Tateishi, Yumiko, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Sali, circa 1999 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Byse, circa 2005 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Richard, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Taylor-Kearney, Carol, circa 2006 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Tedesco, Robin, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Telcocci, Gina, circa 2001 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Teraberry, Peter, circa 2004 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Terruso, Luigi, circa 2004 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Teruya, Yuken, circa 2001 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Thibault, Sarah, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Thiercelin, Thibaud, circa 2006 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Thomassen, Maurice, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Thompson, Sharon, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Thomsen, Tamara, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Throjussen, Tanja, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Tibbs, Millee, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Tice, Michael, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Tijnagel, Arno, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 21)